# **Yoran Essers**

Full Stack Developer

## Profile

Hello, my name is Yoran Essers. I am a Full Stack developer. I see myself as a developer who likes to learn new technologies / techniques and skills. I have a lot of knowledge in the field of website creation and design. I also have a lot of knowledge in the field of making apps and software. At the moment I am mainly studying the making of large web apps. I have had my own company called YEDevelopment for 1.5 years. Here I mainly do projects for others with friends. We do this mainly in the field of Web development and App development. In the software field I mainly have knowledge of the Java language.

## Employment History

## Founder / CEO at YEDevelopment, Netherlands

March 2019 - Present

CEO at YEDevelopment. I'm the founder and current CEO of this company. Currently growing really fast and I love working here. It is great to see projects ending and happy costumers.

## Developer at GeoCraftNL, Netherlands

February 2019 - July 2020

Developer at GeoCraftNL. Mainly making plugins for there Minecraft server and some Web developing work. I learned a lot here and had a really great time.

## Education

## Elementary School, Op Gen Hei, Landgraaf

August 2010 - June 2018

My Elementary School in the Netherlands. Started my coding journey here.

## WebDev Master Grade, EasyDevCollege, Utrecht

December 2018 - Present

Started learning the basics of development. Now we are learning deeper things about big web applications.

#### Havo, Eijkhagen, Landgraaf

August 2018 - Present

Basic training in the Netherlands.

September 2020 — September 2020

## Courses

## Full React/Redux/SocketIO (and more) Course, Udemy

January 2019 - Present

## HTML5 / CSS3 Course, Udemy

July 2019 — Present

#### Details

Generaal Hodgesstraat 27, Landgraaf, 6374TL, Nederland, 0681696454

### yoranpcbuilding@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth 06-05-2006 Landgraaf

#### Skills

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

React

Java

Swift

Flutter

Python

C#

PHP

Vue and Angular

SQL

#### Languages

Dutch

English

German

French